本字幕由 ShinY 深影字幕组 原创翻译制作
深影字幕组论坛地址 http://shinybbs.com
翻译： 药材 许块块 HTC 打狗棒
校对： 闲鱼一条 iamazed   后期： 大逋
我是黛比・韦弗
My name is Debbie Weaver.
这是我的家人
This is my family.
这是我们过去在新泽西贝永的家
This is our old apartment in Bayonne, New Jersey.
我丈夫马蒂在镇上给我们找了一个新房子
My husband Marty got us a deal on a town house...
邻居和蔼 街道宽阔
nicer neighborhood, wider streets.
只有一个小小的问题
Just one little problem...
我们的邻居全部来自另一个星球
our neighbors are all from another planet...
这不是玩笑
Literally.
姜饼人
伯克小学
马蒂看啊
Look at this, Marty.
我们在这可以做很多事
There's so much to volunteer for.
在这里我们也许真的可以做些有意义的事呢
We could make a real difference at this school.
这真无聊 人类真是无趣
This is boring. Humans are boring.
拉里・伯德太淡定了
Larry Bird is underwhelmed.
那你怎么不找点有趣的事去做?
Well, why don't you find something that interests you?
比如 我们准备参加家长教师联谊会
Yeah, like, I think we're gonna join the P.T.A.
你想说啥?
What? What was that?
不好说 家教会?
I don't know. The P.T.A.?
也许今年我们可以尝试下别的事情
I mean, maybe this year we should volunteer for different things.
我可以去教足球
You know? I could coach soccer.
噢 当教练
Oh, coaching.
好吧 你有意见?
Okay, what was that?
我喜欢你做教练 好喜欢
I love when you coach. Love it.
是你说要做点有意义的事情
Well, you talk about making a difference.
做教练很有意义
Well, coaching is it.
还有什么比运动
What's better than molding young minds
更能磨练孩子们的意志 是吧?
through organized athletics, right?
- 噢 听起来不错 - 马蒂 拜托
- Oh, that sounds interesting. - Come on, Marty.
只不过就是你一边吹哨子 孩子们一边
It's you blowing a whistle while a bunch of kids
像一群疯牛一样在球场上乱跑
run across a field like a herd of confused cattle.
你当他们是曼联队啊
It's hardly Manchester United.
家长教师协会又是做什么的?
What does this, uh, P.T.A. do exactly?
- 帮助学校... - 点心义卖
- It helps the school... - Bake sales.
点心义卖只是其中一个很小的部分
Bake sales are a small part of it.
可以借此开展文化项目
It's also a chance to install an arts program.
是啊 之后就是你争我吵 勾心斗角
Yeah, and get mired in bickering and petty politics.
你争我吵 勾心斗角? 听上去真不错
Bickering and petty politics? Oh, that sounds delightful.
就像察布隆伊恩的议会
Just like zabvronian council.
夫人 我和黛比・韦弗去参加家长教师联谊会
Wife, I think I will join Debbie Weaver on this T.P.A.,
而你可以和马蒂教孩子们踢球
and you can coach soccer with Marty.
噢 太好了!
Oh, excellent!
等会儿 你对运动了解吗?
Now hold on. Do you even know anything about sports?
当然 小时候我并不是很出众
Oh, yes. I was nothing exceptional as a child,
但体育极大地补足了我的自信
but sports gave me some much-needed self-esteem.
真希望我们的小迪克也能像我一样
I was hoping that our little Dick might follow in my footsteps.
你为啥和我过不去?
Why are you fighting me?
保重 教练
Good luck, coach.
呃 都是陈词滥调
Well, this is boilerplate stuff.
你说察布隆伊恩的议会也兴这一套?
You say this is similar to your Zabvronian council?
那你应该能很快适应这儿
You should have no trouble keeping up.
你们的"希望屠夫"呢?
Where's your butcher of hope?
高个子 戴着黑色兜帽 来隐藏他无尽的悲伤
Tall chap, wears a dark hood to mask his eternal sorrow.
所有争论的终结者
Puts an end to debates.
没有他 会议怎么能正常进行?
How can you have a proper meeting without a butcher of hope?
也许先跳过这项
Maybe skim this.
下一项议程是 点心义卖 筹资买新球服
The next item on the agenda is the bake sale for the new soccer uniforms.
经过深思熟虑
Now, after giving it a lot of thought,
我决定卖巧克力饼
I've decided we'll sell brownies.
都同意是吗?
All in favor?
打搅一下 我叫黛比・韦弗
Ooh! Excuse me. I'm Debbie Weaver,
- 马克斯和艾比的妈妈 - 你好黛比
- Max and Abby's mom. - Hello, Debbie.
虽然我不认识你的孩子 但你肯定告诉过他们
I don't know your children, but I'm sure you've taught them
打断别人说话是很失礼的
how rude it is to interrupt someone.
哦 呵呵
Oh. Fun.
好的 我有个想法
Well, uh, okay. I have a couple of ideas.
原来在贝永的学校
Back at our old school in Bayonne,
我们都用姜饼作主打
we made gingerbread cookies for the bake sale,
姜饼做成球队的形状
and we decorated them like the soccer team,
很受孩子们欢迎
and the kids loved 'em.
所以每次都能赚到很多...
And we ended up making a lot of m...
钱
Money.
我们做了...
We made...
很多...
it was a lot of...
姜饼... 都很好吃
They were... delicious.
原来主席就是你们的"希望屠夫"
The president has become your butcher of hope.
- 这可不是好兆头 - 闭嘴!
- Nothing good can come of this. - Just zip it!
谢谢你 黛比
Thank you, Debbie.
在贝永 你们能就地取材做点心
I'm sure in Bayonne, you used what you had,
我很佩服 但这里的情况不同
and I admire that, but we have different standards here.
所以还是做巧克力饼吧
So we'll be making brownies.
太不讲理了! 马蒂是对的
This is ridiculous! Marty was right.
家教会果然尽是勾心斗角 我们走
The P.T.A. Is just petty politics. Let's go.
不能善罢甘休
We shall do no such thing.
这女人不仅否定你的观点
This woman is not only attacking your idea,
还否定了你 你的生活方式和你的孩子
she's attacking your very being, your way of life, your children.
她只是喜欢巧克力饼罢了
I think she just likes brownies.
抱歉
Excuse me.
协会手册规定
According to your guidelines,
与筹资相关的任何议程
any decisions regarding fund-raising
需由全体人员投票表决
must be voted upon by the entire group.
因此 我动议 通过投票...
Therefore, I move we vote...
来决定是卖姜饼还是巧克力饼
gingerbread men or brownies?
我附议
I second the motion.
好 下周进行投票
Fine. Next week, you'll have your vote.
- 现在咋办? - 分而治之
- What do we do now? - Divide and conquer.
只要琳达不在 说服他们就会简单些
When Linda's not around, it'll be easier to convince them.
我们一个一个拿下他们
We'll go after them separately.
一个一个搞定
Ooh! Pick 'em off one by one.
是的 只要我俩齐心 银河系唾手可得
Yes, and together, we shall rule the galaxy.
- 啥? - 没啥
- What? - What?
小伙子们 跑起来!
Keep moving, guys!
跑起来! 传球!
Keep it going! Pass the ball!
干的不错 迪克踢得不错
Nice work, Dick. Way to get a piece of that ball.
你真棒
It's a great job.
我不懂 真心不懂
I'm confused. I'm very confused.
看上去 迪克表现很糟
It would appear that Dick is not doing a great job.
实际上 他是队里最差的球员
In fact, I would say that he is the worst player on the team,
但你仍说他做的很好
and yet you keep lying about his performance.
听着 杰西 做教练就是要积极强化
Listen, Jackie, coaching's about positive reinforcement.
好吧 说实话 这孩子绝对成不了贝克汉姆
Okay, let's face it, kid's never gonna be David Beckham.
我们本准备给他起这个名字的
We almost named him David Beckham.
我倒觉得 只要稍加训练
As a matter of fact, I think with some practice,
迪克就可以成为地球上最伟大的球员
Dick could be the greatest soccer player the world has ever seen.
实则不然
Yeah, not so much.
要是我 我就不会抱这么高的...期望
I would lower those expectations... a lot.
也许以后 他会长得像大卫・贝克汉姆
Well, maybe he could at least grow up to look like David Beckham.
不太可能吧
Mm, nope.
不过也许我们鼓励他 他会玩的很开心呢
But if we encourage him, he'll probably have a good time.
加油 小伙子们 跑起来 动起来
Come on, guys, keep it going! Move it along!
拦住球 迪克!
Get the ball, Dick!
就是这样! 漂亮 迪克!
That's it! Way to go, Dick!
小伙子 你这次都快碰到球了呢
You almost made contact that time, buddy!
谢谢 感觉好多了 教练
Thanks. Felt great, coach.
好吧 真心不是贝克汉姆的料
Yeah, not David Beckham.
记住 你比那些女人强大 黛比・韦弗
Remember, you are stronger than these women, Debbie Weaver.
她们要么听你的话 要么领略你的怒火
They must do your bidding or feel your wrath.
噢 谢了 拉里
Oh, thanks, Larry.
有个男人在背后支持的感觉真好
You know, it's nice to have a man supporting me on this.
我牙上有口红吗?
Do I have lipstick on my teeth?
有 我还以为你是故意抹的
Yes, but I thought that was on purpose.
嗨 伊丽莎白
Hi... Elizabeth.
很抱歉来打扰你
I'm sorry to bother you at home,
不过我们想说你有没有个一两分钟
but we were wondering if you had a few minutes
来谈谈点心义卖的事
to talk about the bake sale.
我真的不太关心这事儿
I really haven't thought much about it.
我一般跟着琳达投票 等我决定好会告知你的
I usually just vote with Linda, but I'll let you know.
伊丽莎白 黛比・韦弗为了见你
Elizabeth, Debbie Weaver has spent all morning
花了一早上的时间给牙齿涂口红
putting lipstick on her teeth to come talk to you.
我恳请你听她说完
I insist you hear her out.
他对家教会超级上心的
He's very passionate about the P.T.A.
好吧
Okay.
不过上次我投琳达反对票
But the last time I voted against Linda,
我女儿可是一整年没有玩伴
my daughter didn't have a playdate for, like, a year.
她又矮又胖 她需要尽可能多的朋友
She's kinda chunky. She needs all the friends she can get.
这正是整件事如此重要的原因
And that's why this is so important,
- 因为家教会是为所有人服务的 - 所有人
- because the P.T.A. is about everyone. - Everyone.
不是一个人
Not just one person.
对 今天只是个饼干
Yes, today it's about cookies.
明天也许是禁止你的胖丫头上学校年鉴
Tomorrow it's banning your potbellied daughter from the yearbook.
伊丽莎白 将心比心
Elizabeth, mother to mother,
我们不能让琳达得逞
we can't let Linda get away with this.
进来吧
Come in.
太棒了
Excellent.
再说 姜饼干比巧克力蛋糕卡路里少多了
Plus gingerbread cookies have fewer calories than brownies.
我知道你喜欢给孩子吃健康食品
I know you like to feed your kids healthy foods.
我知道你有一个博客专门讲这个
I know you have a blog about it, yeah.
听着 特蕾西 我得去做饭了
Listen, Tracy, I gotta start making dinner.
我指着你投票了好吗
Can I count on your vote?
真的? 太好了 谢谢
Yeah? Great! Thanks!
我滴个神啊 您这短裤
Oh, dear lord, those shorts.
是啊 还挺合身的
Yeah, they still fit.
是吗?
Do they?
- 训练如何? - 太棒了
- How was your practice? - It was awesome.
你猜怎么着? 我真心觉得我做的事特有意义
You know what? I really feel like I'm starting to make a difference.
你呢?你的小饼干生意怎么样啊?
How about you? How is your little, uh, cookie thing coming?
马蒂 那不是小饼干生意好嘛
It's not a little cookie thing, Marty, okay?
我是在争取家教会的民主化
I'm fighting to keep the P.T.A. democratic.
- 没错 用你的姜饼人 - 没错
- Right. With gingerbread man. - That's right.
我是说 我可不穿着女士裤子
I mean, I'm not chasing little kids around
整天追着小孩屁股后面跑...
in lady pants all day, but...
好嘞 等等 等等
Okay, hold on, hold on.
我没有穿着女士裤子
I'm not chasing kids around
整天追着小孩屁股后面跑好嘛
in lady pants, okay?
我是在创造一辈子的回忆
I'm creating lifelong memories.
好吧 你看怎么着? 我错了
All right, you know what? I'm sorry.
我很高兴你喜欢当教练
I'm glad that you are enjoying coaching.
我只是觉得我们各做各的事十分明智
I just think it was a good decision for us  to do separate things.
是啊 超赞的决定
Yeah, it was a great decision,
我也很高兴你喜欢你的家长教师联谊会
and I'm happy that you're enjoying the P.T.A.
我很高兴你高兴我喜欢你的家教会
Well, I'm happy you're happy I'm enjoying the P.T.A.
那么 跟我说说 黛比・韦弗
So, tell me, Debbie Weaver,
姜饼人尝起来跟其他人一样吗?
does gingerbread man taste the same as regular man?
不
No.
你好 黛比
Hello, Debbie.
出门看看另一半人怎么活?
Out seeing how the other half lives?
嗨 琳达
Hi, Linda.
别告诉我你还在为你的姜饼人召集支持者呢?
Don't tell me you're still trying to drum up support for your gingerbread cookies?
的确如此
We are.
并且我们已经得到必要的票数
And we've just acquired the necessary votes
来否决你巧克力饼 接受事实吧 夫人
to overrule your brownie mandate, so take that, lady.
我当家长教师联谊会的主席已经好久了
You know, I've been president of the P.T.A. for a long time,
你们这种人我也看多了
and I've seen your type come and go.
你搬到郊区
You move to the suburbs
带来你城里的恶习
and bring the bad ideas from the city with you.
我可不允许这一切发生 明白吗?
Well, I'm not gonna let that happen here, okay?
很好 借过
Great. Beep-beep.
天啊
Ow, God.
主席
她对家教会还真上心
Wow. She's really into the P.T.A.
也许我们就该让她随心所欲
Maybe we should just let her do what she wants.
坚决不行
Absolutely not.
我有把握确保我们成功
I have a plan that will guarantee us victory.
真的? 好吧
Yeah? Okay.
但别做什么怪事
But don't do anything weird.
你就挺怪的
You're weird.
晚上好 夫君
Good evening, husband.
好啊 夫人
Oh, hello, wife.
你看起来心事重重 怎么了?
Oh, you look troubled. What's the matter?
迪克今天参加足球训练
Dick had soccer practice today.
他真的糟透了 但是马蒂・韦弗
And he was really quite awful, but Marty Weaver
一直告诉他做的很好
kept on telling him he was doing a good job.
他把这叫做"积极强化"
He called it "positive reinforcement."
这群人类和他们那套每个人都是独一无二的的鬼话
Oh, these humans and their "everyone's special" baloney.
衰人们 尽情享受被人修理的快乐吧
Have fun sucking hind teat to the rest of the universe, losers.
我十分担心如果迪克在运动方面如此差劲
Uh, I'm very concerned that if Dick is a poor athlete,
他会缺乏自信 就不能成为
he'll lack self-esteem and fail to grow up
像他妈妈一样坚强自信的黑人女性
to be a strong, confident black woman like his mother.
我在运动中找到了自我 我希望他也能如此
I found myself in sport. I was hoping he would, too.
也许该由你来主导局势了
Well, you might need to take more control of the situation.
这些人类太过柔弱
These humans are surprisingly soft.
他们需要有人强迫他们行动起来
They must be pushed into action.
你知道什么对你儿子是最好的
You know what's best for your son.
你必须强悍起来 绝不手软
You must be fierce and take no prisoners.
- 我不知道 夫君 - 不 你能行的
- Ooh, I don't know, husband. - Yes, you can do this.
坚决果断 绝不手软
Be fierce and take no prisoners.
跟着我说
Say it with me.
- 坚决果断 绝不手软 - 坚决手软..不对...我..对不起
- Be fierce and take no prisoners. - Fierce and prisoners... no... I... sorry.
差不多吧
Well, it's close enough.
如果实在不行
And if all else fails,
在迪克的脑袋里装个运动芯片总是行的
we can always install a performance chip in Dick's brain.
- 谢谢老公 - 不客气 亲爱的
- Thanks, Boo. - Welcome, Snookems.
雷吉・杰克逊 就位了吗?
Reggie Jackson, are you in position?
是的 父亲 目标已锁定
Yes, father. Target acquired.
激活姜饼人装置
Activate gingerbread device.
明白
Understood.
琳达?
Linda?
Oh, Linda?
嗨 琳达!
Hi, Linda!
琳达?
Linda?
你好?
Hello?
谁在外面?
Is somebody there?
谁在那儿?
Who's there?
琳达!
Linda!
有人在这儿?
Is somebody here?
你好 琳达
Hello, Linda.
下一个...
The next...
下一个议...议程安排是...
The next item on the age-agenda...
- 那是什么?! - 什么什么?
- What was that?! - What was what?
她看起来好紧张
She seems so nervous.
- 我想她知道我们拉到票了 - 有可能
- I think she knows we got the votes. - Perhaps.
也可能是因为我昨晚在她家对她做了点什么
Or... perhaps she's suffering from post-traumatic stress disorder
让她现在出现了创伤后应激障碍
from something I may or may not have made happen at her house last night.
你做了什么?
What did you do?
我击败了她
I defeated her.
在我们星球 我们通过心理战来打赢战争
Where I'm from, we wage war through psychological destruction.
我们的目标是在精神上重创敌人
Our goal is to mentally crush our enemies
直到他们无法在社会立足
until they can no longer function in society.
我只是想做姜饼
I just wanted gingerbread cookies.
如你所愿
And gingerbread cookies you shall have.
打扰一下
Excuse me.
我有个关于点心义卖的问题
I have a question regarding the bake sale.
别过来 姜饼人!
Stay away from me, gingerbread man!
家教会是你的了 黛比・韦弗
The P.T.A. is yours, Debbie Weaver.
好吧... 真该死
Well... crap.
我知道你很累 迪克
I know you're tired, Dick,
但这是为了你好
but this is for your own good.
谢谢 妈妈 你说得对
Thank you, mother. You were right.
腹部的疼痛确实会变得麻木
The pain in my side did eventually go numb.
嘿! 这是怎么回事?
Hey! What's going on?
我们在挑战体能极限
We're running motivational laps.
这已经是第三百一十圈了
This is 310.
我在尽我所能保护我的儿子
I'm doing what I must to protect my son.
我不想他重蹈我童年的覆辙
I don't want him to have the same childhood I did.
足球队的! 快过来!
Let's go, team! Come on!
都过来! 集合了!
Gather round! Bring it in!
听着 明天是我们的第一场比赛
Listen, tomorrow is our first game, okay?
如果我们参加了就要全力以赴
And if we go out there and we do the best we can
享受比赛 我想我们能赢!
and we have some fun, I think we can win!
不不不不不
No, no, no, no, no.
我们本能赢 但是我们赢不了
We can win, but we won't.
为什么赢不了呢?
And why not?
因为我们有短板
Because there is a weak link among us.
说的就是你 迪克・布特克斯
It's you, Dick Butkus.
你的弱势太明显了很难弥补
Your weaknesses are simply too strong to overcome.
- 所以你得离队 - 什么?
- And therefore you are off the team. - What?
你对我能力的评价直率但准确
Your assessment of my abilities is blunt but precise.
我愿意离队
I shall take my leave.
你不能把他踢出队伍
You can't kick him off the team.
可他是最弱的一个
Oh, well, he's the weakest,
我必须坚决果断绝不手软
and I must be fierce and take no prisoners.
这样能促使他更加努力
It will motivate him to work harder.
好吧 但我才是教练 我说了让他留下
Okay, well, I'm the coach, and I say that he stays.
好吧 那你也离队 马蒂
Fine. You're off the team, Marty.
你不能踢我走! 我是教练!
You can't kick me off! I'm the coach!
全队听着 投票表决
Team, loyalty vote.
你们是愿意跟随我走向胜利
Would you rather follow me to victory
还是愿意跟着韦弗教练走向失败?
or coach Weaver to certain defeat?
现在就选
Choose now!
马克斯?
Max?
好啦 爸爸! 瞧瞧她这短裤!
Come on, dad! Look at her in those shorts!
我可不是小孩子了
I just got puberty.
是啊
Yeah.
往好地方想想 教练
Look on the bright side, coach.
你穿短裤也挺好看的
You also look good in your shorts.
看见没?
See?
积极强化并不奏效
Positive reinforcement doesn't really work.
训练得如何?
How was practice?
杰西让我泪流满面
Jackie made me cry.
因为她让我觉得我有多棒...
Because she made me feel so good about myself...
我也确实感觉很好
Which I do. I feel really good about me.
你懂的 我做了这么有意义的事儿
You know, 'cause I'm making such a difference, you know?
你呢? 点心义卖办得如何?
What about you? How's the bake sale coming?
非常好 棒极了 也是意义非凡
Awesome. Excellent. Also making a difference.
有拉里・伯德帮忙 整个家教会都听我的
With Larry Bird, the P.T.A. is all mine.
绝无异议
Literally.
挺好
Yeah.
好吧 那我去洗个澡
All right, well, I'm gonna go take a shower.
我要去烤饼干了
I'm gonna go bake the cookies.
我自我感觉真挺好
But I feel really good about myself
因为确实做了有意义的事儿
'cause I'm making a difference.
我就更别提了
Well, I'm even gladder
我做的就更有意义了 所以...
that I'm making more of a difference, so...
杰西说我大腿说得没错
Jackie was right about my thighs.
帮我们做饼干的帮手呢?
Where are the minions to make our cookies?
我鼓舞士气来了
I'm here to motivate their labor.
没有帮手 拉里 一个也没有
The minions quit, Larry. Every single one of 'em.
他们都觉得你是个危险的疯子
They all think you're a dangerous lunatic,
而且我同意他们
and I agree with them.
鼠目寸光的傻子
Oh! Short-sighted fools.
他们显然是不配让你来领导的
They're obviously not worthy of your leadership.
没有他们你会做得更棒的
You're better off without them.
我不同意 您没看到
Well, I would disagree, since now you and I...
咱俩得做两百个姜饼
have to make 200 gingerbread cookies
而且明早前就得做好
by tomorrow morning by ourselves.
啥?
What?
不 我做不来
Oh, no, I can't.
我有点工作上的事儿
I have a, um, a work thing which I have to att...
- 你没有 - 我没有
- No, you don't. - No, I don't.
- 我家猫猫刚死 - 坐下
- My cat just died. - Sit.
咱们动手做吧
Let's get cooking.
嘿 迪克 干嘛呢?
Hey, Dick, what are you doing?
我在练习 这样我就有机会归队了
I'm practicing so that I might return to the team
我妈也会对我另眼相看
and regain my mother's respect.
但目前看来 完全没戏
So far, it's been a total disaster.
其实有时候是父母太把体育当回事了
Well, you know, sometimes parents take sports a little too seriously.
事实上我觉得
And the truth is, I think this might be
这件事的问题在于你妈 不是你
more about your mom than you.
但不可否认的是
But you must admit, by all metrics,
我的体育真的太弱了
I am a pretty bad athlete.
弱爆了 但这不意味着
Oh, the worst. But that doesn't mean
你妈没有为你而骄傲
that your mother isn't proud of you.
我感觉她在你这么大的时候和你一样
I think you're a lot like she was at this age,
体育真的帮她建立了自信
and sports really helped her with her self-esteem.
她希望你也可以这样
And she just wants that same thing for you.
但我又不缺自信
But I'm not lacking self-esteem.
我为啥要没自信? 你看
Why would I be? I mean, look at me.
谁人能有这等姿色?
Who else do you think could pull off this look?
还真不是一般人
Wow, not many.
你是个好孩子 迪克・布特克斯
You're a good kid, Dick Butkus.
快去穿上队服
Why don't you go get your uniform on?
让你归队啦
We're gonna go get you back on that team.
二 四 六 八!
Two, four, six, eight!
二 四 六 八! 二 四 六 八!
Two, four, six, eight! Two, four, six, eight!
迪克?
Dick?
不惜任何代价取得胜利
Win at all costs.
坚决果断 绝不手软
Be fierce. Take no prisoners.
我一点儿都不想我儿子
I don't miss my son at all.
姜饼人!
Gingerbread cookies!
点心义卖 美味小姜饼
帮助球队买新队服
Help the soccer team buy new uniforms.
很好吃哦
They're yummy.
吃起来比看起来美味
They can't taste worse than they look.
不管怎么说我觉得我们还是赢了的
You know, in spite of everything, I think this was quite a victory.
真的? 你这么觉得 拉里?
Do you? Do you, Larry?
我们一块饼干都没卖出去
We've sold zero cookies.
所有家长们都和我们保持距离
Alienated the parents of all our kids' friends,
把一个女人搞疯了
drove a woman crazy,
还做了人类史上
and made the worst gingerbread cookies
最难吃的姜饼
in the history of mankind.
哪来的胜利 拉里?
So, why? Why, Larry?
因为我本来觉得在艺术项目和老师评估方面
Well, because I actually thought you had some pretty good ideas
你是很有想法的
about arts programs and teacher evaluation.
如果有人问我 我会否认 但是
And if anyone ever asks, I shall deny it, but...
如果我需要一个人类女士
If I had to have a human woman
来指导我孩子的教育
guiding my children's education,
我会非常希望是你 黛比・韦弗
I'd be very happy if it were you, Debbie Weaver.
你是个好女人
You are a good human woman.
拉里 你的话让我感动死了
That is actually a very sweet thing to say, Larry.
- 别这么怪怪的 - 不 你才怪
- Please don't be weird. - No, you're weird.
- 好吧 是挺怪的 - 是的
- Okay, well, this is weird. - It is.
上 上!
Go, go!
你好 教练妈妈
Hello, coach mother.
你好 儿子
Hello, son.
马蒂 你来我的球场干啥
Marty, what are you doing on my field?
你得让迪克归队
You need to put Dick in the game.
不 不行
No, I can't.
别这样 杰西 他又不是你
Oh, come on, Jackie. This isn't you.
我知道你担心迪克的自尊心受挫
I know you're worried about Dick's self-esteem,
但没必要 迪克很强大的
but you don't have to be. Dick is a great kid!
瞧瞧他 聪明 有同情心
Look at him. He's smart, he's compassionate.
还很可爱
Huh? He's cute.
等我学会了敲防弹门的笑话
And once I learn a couple of bulletproof "knock-knock" jokes,
- 我就天下无敌了 - 瞧见没?
- I'll be the total package. - You see that?
我就没见过哪个大人有他这么自信
I mean, I don't know an adult who's that confident.
我就是担心
I just worry.
孩子们总是对那些特殊的孩子很残酷
Kids can be so cruel to unique children.
虽然你很不一般
Although you are really quite remarkable.
好吧
Okay.
加油 伙计 穿上
Here you go, buddy. Put these on.
你是个好教练 马蒂・韦弗
You are a good coach, Marty Weaver.
- 还好啦 - 嗯
- I'm okay. - Mm.
漂亮 迪克!
Nice try, Dick!
不是吧
No, it wasn't.
拉里・伯德! 能说点鼓励的话吗!
Larry Bird! Say something encouraging!
- 好吧 - 我是认真的
- Fine. - Honestly.
- 头发很飘逸啊 儿啊 - 是的呢!
- Your hair looks great, son! - Yes!
从你这遗传的
He gets that from you.
谢谢 是从我这遗传的
- Thank you. Yes, he does.
- 神啊 他太糟了 - 我知道
- Oh, God, he's terrible. - I know.
嘿
Hey.
我能买块饼干么?
Can I buy a cookie?
别了吧 除非你想品尝失败的滋味
I wouldn't. Unless you like the taste of failure.
所以说我们该一起干活的
You know, this is why we should do this stuff together,
因为我觉着我们配合的不错的
because I think we make a pretty good team.
不是吧 我们配合是超好的
Oh, come on. We make a great team.
有人说我是很棒的教练
You know, I've been told that I'm a fantastic coach.
有人说我是个好女人
Well, I've been told that I'm a pretty good human woman, so...
你怎么办到的?
How did you do it?
嗨 琳达 什么怎么办到?
Hi, Linda. Do what?
姜饼人 它是活的!
The gingerbread man... it was alive!
我不知道是怎么办到的 但它是活的
I don't know how, but it was alive.
我觉得就是突然然间发生太多事 你没适应好
You know, I think you're just stressed out from the drama of everything.
根本没有活的姜饼人 琳达
There's no such thing as a living gingerbread man, Linda.
真的?
Oh. Really?
把球捡回来 迪克!
Get the ball, Dick!
我跑的够快了!
I'm running as fast as I can!
她好活泼哦
She's a little jumpy.
是的 有点敏感
Yeah, a little high-strung.